Guide to the Sarabande Books Records, 1990-2022 RL.01137
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2015-0151), 2009-2015, 3 boxes
  - Administrative Materials, 2012-2015
    - Subrights, 2013-2014 (Box 3)
    - Royalty reports, 2012-2014 (Box 3)
    - Reviews (Box 3)
- Accession (2016-0311), 2011-2016
  - Author files
    - Binder, L. Annette/Rise: Stories, 2012-08 (Box 1)
    - Bingham, Sallie/Mending: New and Selected Stories, 2011-08 (Box 1)
    - Bohince, Paula/The Children, 2012-04 (Box 1)
    - Bohince, Paula/Swallows and Waves, 2016-01 (Box 1)
    - Crane, Patty; Transtromer, Tomas/Bright Scythe: Selected Poems by Tomas Transtromer, 2015-11 (Box 1)
    - Cramer, Steven/Clangings, 2012-10 (Box 1)
    - Davis, Lydia/The Cows, 2011-03 (Box 1)
    - Dolven, Jeff/Speculative Music: Poems, 2013-07 (Box 1)
    - Dwyer, Joanne Dominique/Belle Laide: Poems, 2013-04 (Box 1)
    - Ermelino, Louisa/Malafemmena, 2016-08 (Box 1)
    - Friedman, Jason K./Fire Year, 2013-11 (Box 1)
    - Fleischmann, T./Syzygy, Beauty, 2012-04 (Box 1)
    - Gustine, Amy/You Should Pity Us Instead, 2016-02 (Box 1)
    - Heise, Thomas/Moth; or how I came to be with you again, 2013-07 (Box 1)
    - Hernandez, David/Hoodwinked, 2011-07 (Box 1)
    - Homolka, Michael/Antiquity, 2016-07 (Box 1)
    - Horrocks, Caroline/This Is Not Your City, 2011-06 (Box 1)
    - Jarman, Mark/Bone Fires: New and Selected Poems, 2011-02 (Box 1)
    - Martens, Amelia/The Spoons in the Grass Are There to Dig a Moat, 2016-04 (Box 2)
    - Jarman, Mark/The Heronry, 2017-01 (Box 1)
    - Kasischke, Laura/If a Stranger Approaches You: Stories, 2013-01 (Box 1)
    - Kimbrell, James/Smote, 2015-10 (Box 1)
    - Lee, Michael Jeffrey/Something in My Eye: Stories, 2012-01 (Box 1)
    - Mathis, Cleopatra/Book of Dog: Poems, 2012-12 (Box 2)
    - McManus, John/Fox Tooth Heart, 2015-11 (Box 2)
    - Mullins, David Philip/Greetings from Below, 2011-01 (Box 2)
    - Null, Matthew/Allegheny Front, 2016-05 (Box 2)
    - Orr, Gregory/The City of Poetry, 2012 (Box 2)
    - Ossip, Kathleen, 2011-05 (Box 2)
    - Passarello, Elena/Let Me Clear My Throat, 2012-08 (Box 2)
    - Petrosino, Kiki/Hymn for the Black Terrific, 2013-07 (Box 2)
    - Purapura, Lia/Rough Likeness: Essays, 2011-12 (Box 2)
    - Shapiro, Lauren/Easy Math, 2013-02 (Box 2)
    - Skinner, Jeffrey/The 6.5 Practices of Moderately Successful Poets, 2012-05 (Box 2)
    - Thomas, Wayne; Branscum, John/Red Holler: Contemporary Appalachian Literature, 2013-10 (Box 2)
    - Van Meter, Ryan/If You Knew Then What I Know Now, 2011-04 (Box 2)
    - Vigderman, Patricia/Possibility: Essays Against Despair, 2013-04 (Box 2)
    - Wade, Julie Marie/Small Fires, 2011-11 (Box 2)
    - Williams, C.K./Catherine's Laughter, 2013-09 (Box 2)
    - Wing, Catherine/Gin and Bleach, 2012-08 (Box 2)
    - Zandi, Jordan/Solarium: Poems, 2014-05 (Box 2)
    - K.A.M. Prize, 2015 (Box 2)
    - Mary M.C. Award, 2015 (Box 2)
- Accession (2018-0011), 2015-2018
  - Administrative Materials
    - Marketing and Publicity, 2017-2018 (Box 1)
    - Budget Conversation, 2017-2018 (Box 1)
    - Contests, 2016-2017; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Authors With Agents (Box 1)
  - Author Files
    - Karyna McGlynn/Hothouse, 2015-2016 (Box 1)
    - Edit Meidav/Kingdom of the Young, 2017 (Box 1)
    - Elena Passarello/Animals Strike Curious Poses, 2014-2016 (Box 1)
    - Kiki Petrosino/Witch Wife, 2016 (Box 1)
    - Mary Ruefle/On Imagination, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Mike Scalise/Catastrophe, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Shawn Wen/A Twenty Minute Silence Followed by Applause, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Rachel Arndt/Beyond Measure/New Essays, 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Emily Fridlund/Catapult, 2015 (Box 1)
    - Fenton Johnson/Everywhere Home, 2016 (Box 1)
    - Jenny Johnson/In Full Velvet, 2015 (Box 1)
    - David Martinez/Post Traumatic Hood Disorder, 2016 (Box 1)
  - Sarabande Writing Labs
    - Anthologies, 2014-2018; 10 Volumes (Box 2)
- Accession (2019-0093), 2017-2019
  - Rosellen Brown author file, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Peter Mishler - Fludde, 2016 (Box 1)
  - Nona Caspers author file, 2016 (Box 1)
  - Sandra Cisneros "Puro Amor" story edits, 2017-2018 (Box 1)
  - Sarabande publicity, 2015-2019 (Box 1)
  - Board Meeting materials, 2017-2018 (Box 1)
  - Sallie Bingham
    - Publishing agreement; "Bear" draft, 2019 (Box 1)
    - Treason rehearsal draft with notes from Sarah Gorham, 2005-2018 (Box 1)
    - "Upstate" Edits 1-3, undated; 3 folders (Box 2)
- Accession 2021-0075, 2019-2020
  Scope and Contents
  Includes author files for books published in 2019 and 2020, Sarabande Writing Labs brochure, 2019 and 2020 catalogs, press releases and reviews for 2019 and 2020 books, and annual reports.
  - Files, 2019-2020 (Box 1)
- Accession 2022-0084, 1990; 2010-2022
  Addition contains author files, Sarabande Writing Labs anthologies, catalogs, promotional ephemera, and Flo Gault poetry prize broadsides.
  - Cisernos contracts, 2017 May 12 (Box 1)
  - Whitney Collins: Big Bad, 2019-2020 (Box 1)
  - Isabel Duarte: Even Shorn, 2019-2020 (Box 1)
  - Paul Griner: The Book of Otto and Liam, 2019-2020 (Box 1)
  - Kimiko Hahn: Brood, 2017 (Box 1)
  - Pamela Hart: Mothers Over Nangarhar, 2017-2018 (Box 1)
  - Emma Hine: Stay Safe, 2019-2020 (Box 1)
  - Kate Nuernberger: The Witch of Eye, 2019-2020 (Box 1)
  - Kathy Ossip: July, 2020 (Box 1)
  - Hai-Dang Phan: Reenactment, 2017-2018 (Box 1)
  - Lia Purpura: All the Fierce Tethers, 2017-2018 (Box 1)
  - Joe Sacksteder: Make/Shift, 2017-2018; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Ann Townsend: Dear Delinquent, 2018 (Box 1)
  - Amy Wright: Paper Conversation, 2019-2020 (Box 1)
  - Sarabande Writing Labs Anthologies, 2014-2016; 2 folders (Box 1)
    Contains volumes 1 through 5, as well as a cover (but no content) for volume 6.
  - Catalogs, 2018-2022 (Box 1)
  - Promotional postcards, circa 2018-2022 (Box 1)
  - Promotional pins, stickers, and pamphlets, circa 2018-2022 (Box 1)
  - Flo Gault poetry prize program, 2019 (Box 1)
  - Flo Gault poetry prize broadsides, 1990; 2010-2019 (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Flo Gault poetry prize broadsides, circa 2010-2019 (Oversize-folder 2)